



Summary

Motivated Software Engineering student from The University of Texas at Dallas with 7 years of experience as a Fire Support Specialist in the U.S. Army. Seeking to apply education and previous work experience to improve my current programming, software engineering skills, and practical knowledge.

Skills

- C++, Java, Python programming languages
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, C, R, SQL, GQL
- Programming in Windows, Linux, Mac OS environments
- Microsoft Project, Visual Studio Code, Github

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

• linkedin.com/in/paulonajera

Education and Training

Bachelors of Science University of Texas At Dallas Richardson, TX, Software Engineering, Expected in 12/2021

Experience

MOPH and Redding Software Corporation

Software Developer Training Program 06/2021 to Current

- Built personal website as a first project using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, and Flask web framework.
- Familiarized with Googles Cloud Platform and Services, including Googles App Engine.
- Participated in company's Video Game Project utilizing Unreal Engine to create interior designs and stages of the game.

University of Texas at Dallas

Research Assistant 06/2021 to Current

- Researched aspects of advanced web programming and tools,
 Frameworks and Web Services.
- Summarized various articles that cover different topics in web programming, new technologies, emerging trends and missing pieces of web development.
- Participated in different labs that teach users how to use web development tools, Xampp, PHP, Web Speech API, WebGL, Ruby on Rails, OpenCV, Flask, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

US Army

Fire Support Specialist/Sergeant 01/2012 to 07/2019

- Worked and effectively lead groups of 5-30 diverse and foreign team members.
- Submitted reports and requests as scheduled, using MS
 Office and military database software for military leaders.
- Evaluated job performance and completed evaluation reports for junior team members.
- Prioritized workload and assignment duties, often with very short notice for team members.
- Maintained and preserved up to \$1,000,000 worth of sophisticated equipment.